James E. and Barbara H. Sherman Ghost Town Photograph Collection circa 1865-1975 (bulk 1964-1969)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
James E. and Barbara H. Sherman Ghost Town Photograph Collection circa 1865-1975 (bulk 1964-1975)
MS 562
Sherman, James E.
Sherman, Barbara H.
Photographs, related 35 mm negatives, and research notes produced by James E. Sherman and Barbara H. Sherman for use in their books Ghost Towns of Arizona and Ghost Towns and Mining Camps of New Mexico. Early photographs, comprising about thirty percent of the collection, were reproduced from various Arizona and New Mexico archives. These span from 1865 to 1953 but most were taken between 1880 and 1920. The majority of the photographs, however, were taken by the Shermans between 1964 and 1969 during their research for their books. The images, from the 1960s, are well identified and mainly show abandoned buildings, mine equipment, cemeteries, and landscapes. Earlier photographs may also show buildings and equipment but also present for some towns are images of activities, residents and founders, and newspaper advertisements. A review of the books will give researchers a good idea of the collection.
8 linear ft.
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/ E-Mail: LBRY-askspcoll@email.arizona.edu
Restrictions
There are no restrictions on this collection.
Historical Note
James E. Sherman was a professor of engineering at Pima College in Tucson, Arizona. His wife, Barbara, graduated from the University of Arizona. An interest in travel, camping, and photography led them to collect this material and write two books on ghost towns in Arizona and New Mexico between 1964 and 1974.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into five series.
Series I: Arizona ghost towns photographs and captions, 1865-1969
Series II: New Mexico ghost towns photographs and captions, 1879-1969
Series III: Research cards, circa 1964-1968
Series IV: Negatives, 1964-1969
Series V: Published books and map, 1969, 1975
Scope and Content Note
Photographs and related research notes of and about Arizona and New Mexico ghost towns and mining camps gathered between 1964 and 1969. Early photographs were reproduced from Arizona and New Mexico libraries and archives. These images may show ghost towns, newspaper advertisements, and portraits of people related to the towns, but a few show mining and other activities of active towns. Photographs in the 1960s taken by the Shermans show abandoned buildings, mining equipment, and cemeteries.
A smaller category of images were donated by individuals living in nearby areas and these are usually dated from the town’s active days. The individuals who contributed the photographs include Thomas McMichael (b.1,f.45,47), Ralph Morrow (b.2,f.1), Grant Van Tilburg (b.2,f.31), Charles Bronson (b.3,f.3), Jackie Straley Silveris (b.3,f.19, b.6, f.36). John Southwell (b.3,f.25, b.4,f.21, b.6, f.23,38), Joe Young (b.3, f.29), Ruth Hart (b.4, f.11), Frank Berry Jr. (b.5, f.9, b.6, f.31), James Giles (b.5, f.24), Herman Weisner (b.5, f.28), and Glen Dorsett (b.6, f.21,30).
Highlights related to Arizona ghost towns include a schoolhouse with a 48-star flag (Cherry, Ariz.), an adobe schoolhouse ruin with a returning teacher (Duquesne, Ariz.), the Fairbanks, Ariz. railroad station, an ore car and portal of a small mine with its original signage (Golconda, Ariz.), ore teams and a blacksmith shop (Pinal, Ariz.), boarding houses (McCabe and Big Bug, Ariz.), an auto repair shop (Courtland, Ariz.) and the wooden buildings of Sunnyside, Arizona, a religious colony of the Donnellites.
New Mexico highlights include charcoal ovens (Gardiner, Catskill and San Pedro, N.M.), railroad stations (Engle and San Antonio, N.M.), an image of the Swastika Fuel Co. with automobiles (Swastika, N.M.), a school and children (Organ, N.M.), Japanese coal miners (Navajo,N.M.), jail ruins (Hillsboro, N.M.), and underground locomotive (Madrid, N.M.), school children (Johnson Mesa, N.M.), a town's first printing press (Kingston, N.M.), a boy scout first aid group (Dawson, N.M.), a local bullfight (Chloride, N.M.), and photos of main street, a fire, a freight team, a musician’s band, and people with their belongings in the street following the fire (Mogollon, N.M.)
Index cards contain information gathered from business directories and newspapers about the various locations.
Access Terms
Extinct cities—Arizona—Photographs.
Extinct cities—New Mexico—Photographs.
Arizona—History—Photographs.
New Mexico--History—Photographs.
Mine buildings—Arizona—Photographs.
Mine buildings—New Mexico—Photographs.
Cemeteries—Southwest, New—Photographs.
Japanese—New Mexico—Photographs.
Sunnyside (Ariz.)--Photographs.
Mogollon (N.M.)--Photographs.
Container List
- Arizona ghost towns photographs and captions, 1865-1969; Series I
  This series is arranged alphabetically by town. Photographs and caption cards are filed together.
  - Alamo, Ariz., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alexandra, Ariz., 1876-1903, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Allen City, Ariz., 1874-1884 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Flag, Ariz., 1884 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Aubrey Landing, Ariz. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alto, Ariz., 1909 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Balkan, Ariz., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bellvue, Ariz., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Big Bug, Ariz., 1888-1895, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bradshaw City, Ariz., 1870s, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bumblebee, Ariz., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Calabasas, Ariz., 1870s, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Castle Dome, Ariz., 1877, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Catoctin, Ariz., 1880s (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cedar, Ariz., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cerbat,Ariz., 1965, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cerro Colorado, Ariz., 1865, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Chaparral, Ariz., circa 1888 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Charleston, Ariz., 1880s-1899, 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Cherry, Ariz., 1965, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Chilito, Ariz., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Chloride, Ariz., 1870s, 1910, 1965-1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Christmas, Ariz., 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Chrysotile, Ariz., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Clack (or Oro Plata), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Clarkston, Ariz., 1914-1924, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Cleator, Ariz., 1924, 1965, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Congress, Ariz., 1898-1909, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Constellation, Ariz., 1898-1912, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Contention City, Ariz., 1963-1965, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Copper Creek, Ariz., 1966 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Copper Hill, Ariz., 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Courtland, Ariz., 1909-1920, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Crown King, Ariz., 1910-1928, 1965, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Dos Cabezas, Ariz., 1925, 1966, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Duquesne, Ariz., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Ehrenberg, Ariz., 1930s, 1965, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Fairbanks, Ariz., 1905, 1965, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Fortuna, Ariz., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Frisco, Ariz., 1910-1920, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Galeyville, Ariz., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Germa, Ariz., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Gillette, Ariz., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Gleeson, Ariz., 1909, 1965, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Golconda, Ariz., 1908-1918, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Goldfield, Ariz., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Gold Road, Ariz., 1905-1918, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Greaterville, Ariz., 1880s-1890s, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Gunsight, Ariz., 1884, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Hackberry, Ariz., 1888, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Hamburg, Ariz. (Ramsey Canyon), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Hardyville, Ariz., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Harquahala, Ariz., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Harrisburg, Ariz., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Harshaw, Ariz., 1880, 1892, circa 1922, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Helvetia, Ariz., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Hereford, Ariz., 1900-1914, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Hilltop, Ariz., 1920, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Jerome, Ariz., 1880-1919, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Johnson, Ariz., 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Katherine, Ariz., 1917-1918, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Kofa, Ariz., 1900-1916, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - La Paz, Ariz., 1965, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Las Guijas, Ariz., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Lochiel, Ariz. (Pancho Villa), 1919, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Mammoth, Ariz., 1895-1896 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Maxton, Ariz., undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - McCabe, Ariz., 1965, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - McMillian, Ariz., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Metcalf, Ariz., 1901-1915 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Millville, Ariz., 1965, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Mineral Park, Ariz., 1880, 1965, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mohave City, Ariz., 1880,1904,1965 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mowry, Ariz., 1909, 1965, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - New Virginia, Ariz., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Oatman, Ariz., 1900-1965 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Octave, Ariz., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Old Trails, Ariz., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Oro Belle, Ariz., 1870s-1880s, 1900-1910, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Oro Blanco, Ariz. (new), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Oro Blanco, Ariz. (old), 1966, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Paradise, Ariz., 1875, 1910-1912, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Pearce, Ariz., 1890s-1906, 1965, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Pima, Ariz., undated (no print) (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Pinal, Ariz., 1880s (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Pioneer, Ariz., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Placerita, Ariz., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Poland, Ariz., 1900-1910, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Polaris, Ariz., 1910, 1965, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Polhamas Landing, Ariz., 1870s-1900, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Queen, Ariz., 1881, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Rawhide, Ariz., 1965 (no prints) (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Reymert, Ariz., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Ruby, Ariz., 1920-1930s, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Russelville, Ariz., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Salero, Ariz., 1909, 1953, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - San Xavier, Ariz., 1964 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Sasco, Ariz., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Senator, Ariz., 1880s (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Seymour, Ariz., 1800 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Shultz, Ariz. (also Tiger), 1903, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Signal, Ariz., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Silent, Ariz., 1966 (no prints) (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Silverbell, Ariz., 1905-1907, 1920s, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Silver King, Ariz., 1881-1884, 1965, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Stanton, Ariz., 1880s, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Stockton, Ariz., 1906-1965 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Stoddard, Ariz., 1878, 1906, undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Sunnyside, Ariz., 1938, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Swansea, Ariz., 1965, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Tip Top, Ariz., 1888, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Tombstone, Ariz., 1881-1897, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Total Wreck, Ariz., 1883, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Troy, Ariz., 1965, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Twin Buttes, Ariz., 1905, 1920s, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Vekol, Ariz., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Venezia, Ariz., 1965 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Vulture, Ariz., 1965, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Walker, Ariz., 1880s, 1952, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Washington Camp, Ariz., 1909, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Weaver, Ariz., 1965, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - White Hills, Ariz., 1897-1910, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Misc. mining, 1880-1897, 1965, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Colorado River boats, 1870-1910, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, 1965-1966, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
- New Mexico ghost towns photographs and captions, 1879-1969; (bulk 1967-1969); Series II
  - Allison, NM, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Alma, NM, 1893-1914, 1968, undated (Box 3, Folder 17a)
  - Alumina, NM, 1892 (Box 3, Folder 17b)
  - Amizett, NM, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Ancho, NM, 1905-1918, 1937, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Anchor, NM, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Andrews,NM, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Baldy, NM, 1891, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Blackhawk, NM, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Bland, NM, 1880s-1915 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Blossburg, NM, 1880s-1905 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Bonanza City, NM, 1880s, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Bonito City, NM, 1904 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Brice, NM, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Brilliant, NM (old), 1910-1925, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Cabezon, NM, 1950s, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Canada, NM, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Carbonateville, NM, 1879-1886 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Carlisle, NM, 1900-1916, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Carthage, NM, 1882, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Catskill, NM, 1887-1900, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Cerrillos, NM, 1880s-1891, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Chloride, NM, 1884-1917. 1941, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Clairmont, NM, 1915, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Cloverdale, NM, 1900, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Colfax, NM, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Columbus, NM, 1913-1916, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Cooks, NM, 1900, 1969, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Cooney, NM, 1915, 1968, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Copper City, NM, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Copperton, NM, 1905, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Coyote, NM (see also Hagan NM), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Dawson, NM, 1920s, 1940s, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Diener, NM, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Dolores, NM, 1968, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Elizabethtown, NM, 1898-1901, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Engle,NM, 1882-1890, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Estey City, NM, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Faywood, NM, 1900, 1940, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Fierro, NM, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Fleming, NM, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Gamerco, NM, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Gardiner, NM, 1902-1925, 1939, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Georgetown, NM, 1880s, 1940, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Gibson, NM, 1895-1914, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Glenwoody, NM, 1909, 1968, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Glorita, NM, 1870s-1910s (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Gold Dust, NM, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Golden, NM, 1903, 1968, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Gold Hill, NM, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Grafton, NM, 1882-1900, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Graham, NM, 1968, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Hachita, NM (new), 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Hachita, NM (old), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Hagan, NM, 1953, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Hanover, NM, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Hansonburg, NM, 1892 (Box 5, Folder 4b)
  - Hermanas, NM, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Hermosa, NM, 1885-1900 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Hillsboro, NM, 1880-1900, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Jicarilla, NM, 1884, 1969, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Johnson Mesa, NM (Bell, NM), 1920s, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Kelly, NM, 1884-1915, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Kingston, NM, 1880-1900, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Koehler, NM, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - La Bajada, NM, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Lake Valley, NM, 1882-1890, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - LaVentana, NM, 1928, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Leopold, NM, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Lincoln, NM, 1969, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Madrid, NM, 1920-1940, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Malone, NM, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Mentmore, NM, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Midnight, NM, 1953, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Mineral City, NM, 1882 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Modoc, NM, 1904-1909 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Mogollon, NM, 1914, 1938, 1968, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Navajo, NM, 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Nogol, NM, 1884 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Nutt, NM, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Organ, NM, 1915, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Orogrande, NM, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Otero, NM, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Park City, NM, 1885 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Parsons, NM, 1890, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Philipsburg, NM, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Pinos Altos, NM, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Pyramid, NM, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Rabenton, NM, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Red River, NM, 1881-1900, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Riley, NM, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Robinson, NM, 1882 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Rosedale, NM, 1905, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - San Antonio, NM, 1882-1884, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - San Augustine, NM, 1909, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - San Geronimo, NM, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - San Marcial, NM, 1888 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - San Pedro, NM, 1882-1892, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Santa Rita, NM, 1967, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Sawyer, NM, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Senorito,NM, 1900, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Shakespear, Ariz., 1967, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Steins, NM, 1964, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Sugarite, NM, 1915, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Swastika, NM, 1923-1925, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Sylvanite, NM, 1908-1909, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Terrero, NM, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Trementina, NM, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Twinning, NM, 1885-1893 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Tyrone, NM, 1967,undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Valedon, NM, 1920, 1969, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Van Houten, NM, 1903-1910, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Vera Cruz, NM, 1882 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Virginia City, NM, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Waldo, NM, 1968, undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Weaver, NM, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - White Oaks, NM, 1881-1917, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Winston, NM (Fairview, NM), 1880-1919, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Yankee, NM, 1907-1913, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Apache Indians, 1880s, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - General information, 1880-1913 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1880s-1900, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - General advertisements, 1888-1891 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Santa Fe, NM, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Research cards, circa 1964-1968; Series III
  This series is arranged alphabetically by state then by town.
  - Alexandra, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Aubrey Landing, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - American Flag, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Bellevue, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Big Bug, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Bradshaw, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Bueno, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Bumblebee, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Calabasas, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Castle Dome, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Catoctin, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Cedar, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Cerbat, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Cerro Colorado, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Chaparral, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Charleston, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Cherry, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Chilito, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Chrysotile, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Clarkstown, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Christmas, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Cleator, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Clip, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Cochran, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Columbia, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Congress, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Copper Creek, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Courtland, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Constellation, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Contention, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Copper Hill, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Crown King, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - DeNoon, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Dos Cabezas, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Ehrenberg, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Fairbank, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Fortuna, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Frisco, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Galeyville Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Garces, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Germa, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Gila City, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Gillett, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Gleeson, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Golconda, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Gold Basin, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Goldfield, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Goldflat, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Gold Road, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Greaterville, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Greenwood City, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Gunsight, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Hamburg, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Harqua Hala, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Harrisburg, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Hilltop, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Harshaw, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Helvetia, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Howells, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Jerome, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Johnson, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Katherine, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Kofa, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - La Paz, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Lochiel, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - McCabe, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - McMillenville, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Metcalf, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Middlemarch, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Millville, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Mineral Hill, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Mineral Park, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Mohave City, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Mowry, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Nugget, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Oatman, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Octave, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Old Glory, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Oldtrails, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Olive, Ariz. (also Olive Camp), circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Olive City, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Oro Belle, Ariz. (also Harrington), circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Oro Blanco, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Owens, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Paradise, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Pearce, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Pinal, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Pioneer, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Placerita, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Planet, Ariz. (and Eagle Landing), circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Poland, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Polaris, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Polhamus Landing, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Queen, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Quijotoa, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Reymert, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Richinbar, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Rosemont, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Ruby, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Russellville, Ariz. (Russell Camp), circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Salero, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Sasco, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Senator, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Seymour, Ariz., circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Signal, Ariz. and Liverpool Landing, circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Silent, Ariz. and Norton’s Landing, circa 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 106)